[{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679058194,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":9727,"timeElapsed":57293},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679065405,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":7208,"timeElapsed":64504},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679073031,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":7622,"timeElapsed":72129},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679084678,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":11645,"timeElapsed":83777},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679087465,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2785,"timeElapsed":86564},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679089760,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2292,"timeElapsed":88858},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679092130,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":2367,"timeElapsed":91229},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679101403,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":9271,"timeElapsed":100502},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679105220,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3814,"timeElapsed":104319},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679122529,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":16231,"timeElapsed":121628},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679125182,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2652,"timeElapsed":124281},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679127012,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1827,"timeElapsed":126111},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679129092,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2078,"timeElapsed":128191},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679131841,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":2746,"timeElapsed":130939},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679134016,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":2173,"timeElapsed":133115},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679136450,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2432,"timeElapsed":135549},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679139811,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3359,"timeElapsed":138910},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679141957,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2143,"timeElapsed":141055},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679150335,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":7184,"timeElapsed":149434},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679152563,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2225,"timeElapsed":151662},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679155265,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2700,"timeElapsed":154364},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679157855,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2588,"timeElapsed":156954},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679160933,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3076,"timeElapsed":160032},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679163807,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":2873,"timeElapsed":162906},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679165613,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":1804,"timeElapsed":164712},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679168928,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3313,"timeElapsed":168026},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679171567,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2637,"timeElapsed":170666},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679173457,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1888,"timeElapsed":172556},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679177988,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3577,"timeElapsed":177087},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679179826,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":1836,"timeElapsed":178925},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679182834,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3006,"timeElapsed":181933},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679185355,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2520,"timeElapsed":184454},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679189288,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":3931,"timeElapsed":188387},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679192224,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":2934,"timeElapsed":191323},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679193802,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":1577,"timeElapsed":192901},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679197766,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":3962,"timeElapsed":196865},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679199980,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2212,"timeElapsed":199079},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679206160,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":5142,"timeElapsed":205259},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679208988,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2826,"timeElapsed":208087},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679211139,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2148,"timeElapsed":210238},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679213125,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1984,"timeElapsed":212224},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679215018,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1891,"timeElapsed":214117},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679217491,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2472,"timeElapsed":216590},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679219767,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":2273,"timeElapsed":218866},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679224007,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4238,"timeElapsed":223106},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679231216,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":7207,"timeElapsed":230314},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679236022,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3926,"timeElapsed":235121},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679237417,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1394,"timeElapsed":236516},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679239003,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1584,"timeElapsed":238102},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679240511,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1506,"timeElapsed":239610},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679242302,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1788,"timeElapsed":241401},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679244052,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1748,"timeElapsed":243151},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679246062,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2008,"timeElapsed":245161},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679247798,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1734,"timeElapsed":246896},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679249540,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1740,"timeElapsed":248639},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679260895,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":10262,"timeElapsed":259994},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679262698,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":1801,"timeElapsed":261797},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679264726,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2025,"timeElapsed":263824},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679267787,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3060,"timeElapsed":266886},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679272293,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":4504,"timeElapsed":271392},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679274780,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2485,"timeElapsed":273879},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679276649,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1866,"timeElapsed":275748},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679278809,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2158,"timeElapsed":277908},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679282342,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3530,"timeElapsed":281441},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679284234,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1890,"timeElapsed":283333},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679289612,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":4505,"timeElapsed":288711},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679291056,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1442,"timeElapsed":290155},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679292571,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1513,"timeElapsed":291670},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679294079,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1506,"timeElapsed":293178},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679298789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":4709,"timeElapsed":297888},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679300963,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2172,"timeElapsed":300062},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679302691,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1726,"timeElapsed":301790},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679304498,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1804,"timeElapsed":303597},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679307152,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2652,"timeElapsed":306251},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679316714,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8565,"timeElapsed":315812},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679321266,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":4550,"timeElapsed":320365},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679326714,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":5447,"timeElapsed":325813},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679328426,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1710,"timeElapsed":327525},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679330326,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1898,"timeElapsed":329425},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679332554,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2226,"timeElapsed":331653},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679335138,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2582,"timeElapsed":334237},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679337258,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2118,"timeElapsed":336357},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679339237,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":1976,"timeElapsed":338335},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679345328,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":4928,"timeElapsed":344427},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679348178,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2848,"timeElapsed":347277},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679356611,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":8430,"timeElapsed":355710},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679358101,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1488,"timeElapsed":357200},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679360889,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2786,"timeElapsed":359988},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679363919,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":3028,"timeElapsed":363018},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679366242,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2321,"timeElapsed":365341},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679369751,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3507,"timeElapsed":368850},{"subjectID":"tk4eleh9eu","prolificID":"6699571ba83beb19c5acbfef","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1d325f6bf3f399bfd1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679372325,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2572,"timeElapsed":371424}]